question_data = [{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Japanese Shinkansen beat the French TGV&#039;s speed record for fastest electric rail train.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;I disapprove of what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it&quot; is a quote from French philosopher Voltaire.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Klingons once had a period of Democracy in their history, they referred to it as the &quot;Dark Times&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Wilt Chamberlain scored his infamous 100-point-game against the New York Knicks in 1962.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
